我们几乎99.9%肯定
We can claim with 99.9 percent certainty
该DNA属于格兰特先生
that this DNA comes from Mr. Grant.
你在尸体上或者周围发现了
And did you find any other evidence of DNA
其他DNA证据吗
around or on the body?
没有  只有格兰特先生的
No. Only Mr. Grant's.
同时被害人指缝里的DNA存量
And the quantity of the DNA under the victim's fingernails
也能说明
was consistent...
存在一场自卫挣扎
with a defensive struggle?
-没错  -你能不能...
- That is correct. - And you'd be able to...?
-哪里找到的  -学校安保
- Where'd you get it? - Campus security.
他们很是同情
They were sympathetic.
凯琳达  我真想亲你一口
Kalinda, I could kiss you.
别在这儿
Not here.
听着  我一会儿得和你谈谈
Listen, I-I need to talk to you later.
行  什么事
Sure, about what?
一会儿再说
Later.
那么维尔先生...
So, Mr. Vail...
是维尔医生才对
Actually, Dr. Vail.